[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":46951,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":56306,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</ sub>, yo u start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":20700,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":77013,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2130,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":79149,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":5086,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":84237,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":8191,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":92429,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":9915,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":102347,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1484,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":103833,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3742,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":107577,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1984,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":109563,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6  or bigge r, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":6428,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":115993,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1404,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":117399,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":6668,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":124068,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2 -0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":6516,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":130585,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":7487,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":138074,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":15526,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":153604,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to  perform  +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3404,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":157010,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1424,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":158436,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":" 5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3224,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":161665,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1289,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":162955,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3582,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":166539,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":2458,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":168999,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":31712,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":200721,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Simil arly, 3  is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":99180,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":299903,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":12513,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":312418,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":10384,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":322804,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remembe r, the i nverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":10216,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":333021,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1803,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":334826,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3498,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":338326,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1205,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":339533,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":4680,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":344215,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":4723,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":348940,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under + <sub>6</ sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":6554,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":355496,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":4713,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":360211,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, the inverse of 0 is 0, the inverse of 1 is 5 and the inverse of 5 is 1, the inverse of 2 is 4 and the inverse of 4 is 2, and finally the inverse of 3 is 3. Do you see a relationship between an element and its inverse under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes its what ever adds up so that the answer is 0","response_history":["yes its what ever adds up t","yes its what ever adds up so that the answer is 0"],"rt":29732,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":389945,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":27897,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":417844,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</ sub> 1 + <sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":135397,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":553243,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["Yes","No"],"rt":7767,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":561013,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator unde r +<sub> 6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":2092,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":563108,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3526,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":566635,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub>  5, so yo u can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":2700,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":569337,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":3791,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":573131,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1769,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":574902,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Rem ember, a  generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":2730,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":577632,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1410,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":579044,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, 1 and 5 are generators. However, 0, 2, 3, and 4 are not generators. Try playing with these non-generators and seeing which elements each of them does generate (i.e. which elements you can get by combining each non-generator with itself repeatedly). Do you see relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators unde r +<sub> 6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I am honestly confused with this part.. I dont understand how the others are not generators","response_history":["I am honestly confused with this part.. I dont uderstand how the","I am honestly confused with this part.. I dont uderstand how th","I am honestly confused with this part.. I dont uderstand how t","I am honestly confused with this part.. I dont uderstand how ","I am honestly confused with this part.. I dont uderstand how","I am honestly confused with this part.. I dont uderstand ho","I am honestly confused with this part.. I dont uderstand h","I am honestly confused with this part.. I dont uderstand ","I am honestly confused with this part.. I dont uderstand","I am honestly confused with this part.. I dont uderstan","I am honestly confused with this part.. I dont udersta","I am honestly confused with this part.. I dont uderst","I am honestly confused with this part.. I dont u ders","I  am honestly confused with this part.. I dont uder","I am honestly confused with this part.. I dont ude","I am honestly confused with this part.. I dont ud","I am honestly confused with this part.. I dont understand how the others are not generators"],"rt":261240,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":840286,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":9855,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":850142,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is  5 +<sub> 9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3627,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":853771,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1775,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":855548,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3321,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":858870,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3104,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":861976,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2790,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":864770,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3429,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":868201,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2667,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":870871,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5   because 4+ 1 is less than 9","response_history":["5   because 4+ 1i","5   because 4+ 1 is less than 9"],"rt":17834,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":888707,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3 because 8+4=12 so you subtract 9 because 12 is greater than 9","response_history":["1","3 because 8+4=12 so you subtract 9 because 12 id","3 because 8+4=12 so you subtract 9 because 12 is greater than 9"],"rt":24379,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":913088,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"the identity would be whatever 2 numbers =9","response_history":["the identity would be whatever 2 numbers =9"],"rt":57077,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":970168,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":18126,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":988296,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":2638,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":990937,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 because the 6+3=9","response_history":["6 because the 6+3=9"],"rt":11693,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1002632,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because it cant be used to equal ine withitsef","response_history":["no because it cant be used to equal ine withitsef"],"rt":16222,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1018856,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes because yu can use that number with itself to get to 9","response_history":["yes because yu can use that number wit ","yes because yu can use that number with itself to get to 9"],"rt":17212,"trial_type":"q uestion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1036069,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because you cant use it with itself to get to 9","response_history":["no because you cant use it with itself to get to 9"],"rt":14824,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1050895,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes because you can use it to get to 9 ","response_history":["yes because you can use it to get to 9 "],"rt":17711,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1068607,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you s ome ques tions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":15207,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1083817,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+n=5","response_history":["1+n=5"],"rt":230800,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1314618,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"i have no idea","response_history":["i have no idea"],"rt":13341,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1327965,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I believe if it is a factor of the number it would work","response_history":["I believe if it is a factor of the number it would work"],"rt":32733,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1360699,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":6788,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1367488,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":6950,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1374441,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":4244,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1378687,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"its the only way to get a number for the answer","response_history":["its the only way to get a number for the answer"],"rt":26088,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1404779,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":12165,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1416950,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":" sometime s, it depends on what the number is","response_history":["sometimes, it depends on what the number is"],"rt":25088,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1442040,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":117794,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1559837,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":2479,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1562325,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"39","response_history":["39"],"rt":3198,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1565528,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":3677,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1569207,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"pre calculas","response_history":["pre calculas"],"rt":9636,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1578846,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3818,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1582665,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3195,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1585862,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2805,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1588669,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2490,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1591161,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you  enjoy th is HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2429,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1593592,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":2369,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1595963,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":5498,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1601464,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":2909,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1604374,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"it was fun, I wish I understood a little more of it","response_history":["it was fun, I wish I understood a little more of it"],"rt":12944,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1617320,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"}]